hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Kowski and in this podcast I
talk about ways for coaches trainers and
mentors to scale their businesses using
online tools direct response marketing
I've been in this space for over 21
years and I help people every single
week scale their businesses to success
now today I want to talk about writing
emails and using email marketing email
marketing is an invaluable tool that we
use and getting people on your email
list is the number one most important
thing that you need to do in your
business once you have them on your list
though then what do you actually send to
people and that's what the podcast today
is going to be all about is what I
recommend that you should do and what I
like to do now is we have incredible
access to tools like Claude 35 Sonet
from anthropic if you go to claw. a you
can get access to this right away and be
able to actually use this you just sign
up and sign in with your email address
and they give you access to Claude to be
able to write some of the best quality
emails on the planet overall for you and
your business and so that's what I would
recommend overall is using Claude 35
Sonet or above to be able to do that
okay and so here's what we'll do is I
want to write an email to
promote a Black Friday
special send this
to my warm
Market list about a bundle
of classes included about starting their
business finding their
Niche running Facebook
ads a bonus copyrighting training from
our client growth Accel accelerator
group okay write it in a persuasive
tone and if I go into Claude Sonet and I
tell it to do this and and right away I
was able to just log in and get access
to Claude completely free to be able to
do this and it it's one of the highest
quality email writing tools that's out
there for you if you want to write
exceptional emails for your business you
want to use Claud you cannot sleep on
this it's amazing hope you're doing well
well I'm reaching out to put something
very special that I think you're going
to love especially you've been thinking
about starting and growing your business
for Black Friday only I'm offering my
most comprehensive bundle of events okay
so this is awesome this right here is an
email that I could send out to my list I
didn't have to take 20 minutes and come
up with ideas for it I was able to go
right ahead with this AI tool and be
able to write that let's say that you
want to um you know I'm hosting a live
event November 30th I want people to
register it's all about creating
Instagram ads I'm not actually hosting
an event on that day but I'm using that
as an example so about creating
Instagram ads that
convert and how to set them all up
include an invite to the zoom call and
write it in a persuasive tone
okay and so again no matter what emails
that you're going to come up with Claude
is able to do this and by the way if
you're listening to this you're like
what is he talking about I have on the
YouTube version of this podcast it on my
screen where you can see this here's the
email right here Master Instagram ads in
one day join our Workshop quick question
you're watching your Instagram ad budget
disappear uh let's see I want this email
and we're going to modify it
geared towards beginner coaches who want
to run ads for the first time time to
lowc cost ads and low ticket offers okay
and so it's going to adjust the email
even based on what I just told it right
here and this is how I'm I'm writing
most of our emails that we're sending
out to anybody is I'm using Claude to be
able to do this uh new coach learned R
Instagram ads first without breaking the
bank does this sound familiar excited to
R your coaching business but then the
thought of running Instagram ads feels
overwhelming I get it I was once in your
shoes afraid to spend money on ads
didn't want to waste a startup
budget uh this is perfect for if you're
just starting your business you R ads
before you have a small budget you're
looking to promote a low ticket offer
Tech makes you nervous we're going to
show you how to set up your first
campaign how to start with $5 a day and
scale up the easiest way to find
coaching client so this is amazing this
is again an email written right here
that you can use for this and so Claud
AI is the number one best tool overall
to be able to use
for creating sales copy for I mean for
for creating email copy for writing
emails overall okay and so keep this in
mind keep this in Your Arsenal another
thing another piece of advice that I I
always give people when it comes to
their email marketing is keep a swipe
file what is a swipe file well a swipe
file is a file of emails that are
written from other people that you can
borrow ideas from and so I do is I
actually have a swipe file
account um a swipe file account is an
email account that's in Gmail that's
signed up for a bunch of different
offers I've signed up for every single
thing using this email account for years
um to be able to see what offers are
being sent out to people and these give
me ideas for what to send out to my own
list like if I just go right now into my
swipe file email account and I just type
in the word Black
Friday let's see what what is being sent
for Black Friday right here look at this
these are the Black Friday emails that
are already going out to my list well to
to me from the list right here my Black
Friday course bundle uh because you
snagged early access to my once AE
bundle so here's one thing that I can do
is I can actually copy this email from
the Swip file and I can go here to
Claud and let's go back to our recent
chat all about let's see
writing emails that we were just working
on right now Black Friday launch bundle
okay can you rewrite the Black Friday
email but use the
following as a template for the tone of
writing the email
okay so what I did was I copied this
email that I got from Amy Porterfield
right here and I told it to use it as a
template for my own email okay because
you're getting early access to this I
I'm including four of my best programs
for one the price of one I wonder how
they built such if you ever wonder how
do they build such a successful business
this bundle is for you complete business
launch bundle includes the business
foundation's Master Class Niche Mastery
Workshop Facebook ads in 10
ensive all
right premium copywriting training from
our client accelerator program grab all
of this by this date you'll have a
whopping
$1,500 you'll say whopping $1,500 on my
system to be honest I'm I'm offering it
um and and this what I could say is I
could edit this and I could say okay
great email but my offer is only going
to be $4.95 for the Black
Friday
special okay so it's going to be a very
low ticket offer excited give you early
access for just $4.95 that's not typo
absolutely crazy price includes all of
this value is this much if you grab it
by this you'll save math as in my strong
Su but even I know that's
bananas so again great email to send out
exceptional email in fact that I could
send out to my list right there and so
we need to stop stop overthinking our
email marketing number one you need to
be writing your list often you need to
stay top of mind to your email list you
need to stay in front of them
consistently and that's what's going to
get people to buy from you because again
sales is your number one most important
thing in your business fulfillment and
delivering results to your client is is
important for delivering on what you say
you are promising when they become a
client but you don't have a business if
you're not getting clients if you don't
have people buying from you and becoming
a client and so email marketing is is a
huge part of that strategy is you can
create an offer based on what people
desire okay so here's their desires and
you're going to deliver that you're
going to give them what they
desire and in exchange they're going to
give you
their email address okay and so that's
why once they're on your email address
because you gave them what they
desire if you're if you're a coach if
you're a course creator giving people
what they desire is giving away your
best content giving away your best ideas
in exchange for an email address in
exchange for that email address and
delivering that in the in the form of
like a webinar or something like that
it's not super complicated I think a lot
of people over complicate this process
of getting emails and then once they
have them they're not writing their list
enough they're not emailing their list
enough they're not sending enough emails
they're they're dragging their feet
they're afraid of upsetting people
they're afraid of annoying people with
their emails y'all you got to grow past
that fear and worry of annoying other
people with your
emails for you to be able to have a
successful business you have to
consistently stay top of Mind in front
of people so that they know that you're
there and so develop your swipe file
grow your swipe file sign up go on X go
on Tik Tok go on Twitter go or that's X
go on Facebook go on YouTube go on in
Instagram and click on people's
advertisements leave the many chat
comments on people's posts to get sent
lead magnets and then join their email
list to see what emails they are sending
to people and that's what a swipe file
does is it gives you access to dozens
upon dozens upon dozens of emails that
you can send or modify to your list any
way you want you know if I took this
email right here here's another simple
one right
here let's rewrite
the and and I and I got this from my
swipe file right here it's another type
of email super
short let's rewrite the
email based on the following template
for for style tone and Cadence are based
on the above okay
template here we go let's see what kind
of email it creates based on this we're
prepping our insane offer we're testing
our systems make sure they run smoothly
would you mind testing it for us as a
big thank you for being a tester you can
grab our entire Black Friday bundle for
this much click here to test the system
and lock in your price that is so funny
can you help me test it that's what this
email is all about can you help us test
this out that's actually a pretty great
uh email hook right there okay so I can
go through my swipe file and I can see
which Black Friday emails have been sent
out to people what's going out and then
I can have ai help
me to
rewrite my
emails based on this based on maybe some
ideas or something that's in my swipe
file here's here's one from Groove this
is a software right here here okay let's
see rewrite the email based on the
following
template okay I'm going to paste another
email in there as a template and you're
going to see what it's going to create
follows a similar format to that
template right here someone who's
transformed hundreds of coaching
businesses with these strategies I want
to share something extraordinary with
you if you want to launch your business
the right way find and attract the right
clients create perfect marketing let me
explain why it's possible building your
first business isent to be
overwhelming but even if you have ever
felt like starting a business sounds
like solving a riik cube blindfolded
you're not alone one day you're excited
great so this is another great email and
those are three emails right there over
the course of 13 minutes that for my
Black Friday promo I'm actually going to
go back and I'm going to borrow some of
these I'm going to use them now one of
the things that I recommend to do is
this is take the emails that the AI
creates and become an editor go into
grammarly edit the grammar make sure all
of that's in order and then and then
edit it so that it actually sounds like
you edit things that maybe aren't how
you would say it but what the AI gives
you is it gives you the ability it gives
you a an initial structure that you can
use to get off the ground quickly to
iterate to not have to waste time and
then from there you're able to identify
okay here's an idea for an email let's
send this out let's test this out and as
you start staying consistent with your
emails you're going to be blown away by
the responses that you get you must must
must engage with your email list no
questions about it and so listen if
you're a coach Mentor trainer and you
want to know Jeremiah how can I work
with you further to be able to help me
grow my business I'd love to see you in
my client growth accelerator program I
love to work with you there's a video
below you can actually access in the
description all about how to add 20 new
clients to your business I'm going to
walk you through that process and give
you an opportunity to jump into our
accelerator program in that video video
so check that out as well it's on the
YouTube version of this and grow your
life and we'll talk soon everybody have
a good one
[Music]
[Applause]